我们要做四次最后离开挑战
We are doing four last to leave videos,
每一个挑战的赢家将会在第五场比赛中竞争$100万美元
and the winners of each are competing in a fifth one for one million dollars.
你正在观看本系列的第二个视频
You are currently watching video number two of this series.
第一个是最后下落挑战 下落挑战持续了超过30个小时！
So the first one was last to fall. Last to fall went for over 30 hours!
$100万美元！
A million dollars!
很多了！
It's a lot!
这是尼克（Nick） 他的教练是克里斯（Chris）
This is Nick, and his coach is Chris.
-他们有相配的衬衫 -是啊！
-They have matching shirts. -Yeah!
-我们会赢的！-我们会赢的！
-We gonna win it! -We gonna win!
这是奥马尔（Omar） 他的教练是杰克（Jake）
This is Omar and his coach is Jake.
这是特洛伊（Troy） 他的教练输掉了好几场比赛
This is Troy and his coach is coming off a couple losses.
老弟啊！
Bruh!
我是佩顿（Payton） 他的教练是马库斯（Marcus）
And this is Payton and his coach is Marcus.
他们身体的一个部位必须穿过这条线才能算作一次摇摆
One of their body parts must cross this line for it to count as a swing.
如果他们没有 我们有一个裁判
If they don't, we have a ref.
如果他们不越过线 他们不会出局 但会决定他们是否努力了
If they don't cross it, they're not out, but what'll determine if they're making an effort.
我于心不忍
I'm very distressed.
给你$1美元你退出
Give you a dollar to get out.
你俩可以平分 $50美分
You guys could split it, 50 cents.
尤金！
Yoink!
幸好我还有$1美元
Good thing I have another dollar.
如果你留下 我给你两个$1美元
I'll give you two if you stay.
我们要捉弄一下我们的摄影师
We're gonna prank our cameraman.
打三个！
Hit three!
那很吓人
That was scary.
我聋了
I can't hear now.
我们要做第一个挑战！
We're doing the first challenge!
留在那袋薯条后面 给你个棉花糖
Stay behind that bag of chips. Here's a marsh mallow.
如果你把它放进他的嘴里 你可以推他一分钟
If you land it in his mouth, you get to push him for a minute.
那是什么？
What is that?
哦！
Oh!
什么是什么？
What is what?
是的 是的 来吧！
Yeah, yeah, come on!
孩子 如果你不明白--
Boy, if you don't get--
等等--
Wait--
真 的！
Wow!
其他人都在这里
This is where everyone else was.
但既然你是钱德勒（Chandler） 你可以上去
Since you're Chandler, you can go up here.
哦！
Ooh!
-你不是钱德勒 所以你要回来 -什么？
-And you're not Chandler, so you're back here. -What?
-干得好！-好吧
-Here you go! -All right.
科比！
Kobe!
走吧！
Let's go!
既然他在推你 是不是轻松了？
Now that he's pushing you, is it easier?
轻松多了
Tons easier.
我要确保我说的很清楚 你们不能碰选手
I wanna make sure I'm very clear, you guys cannot touch the contestants
否则红灯将被迫亮起
or the red lights will be forced to come on.
-哦 哦！-看看这个
-Oh, oh! -Look at this,
我不碰他！
I'm not touching him!
哦 看看我！
Ooh, look at me!
哦嘿 看看那个 特洛伊 马库斯 不能碰他
Oh hey, look at that, Troy, Marcus, can't touch him.
不 不 不--
No, no, no--
他碰到你了吗？
Did he get you?
是的 他碰到我了
Yeah, he got me.
特洛伊碰了碰克里斯
Troy touched Chris.
让我来告诉你们 如果一个参赛者碰到你们中的一个会发生什么
Let me show you what happens if a contestant touches one of you.
天哪 天哪！
Oh my--- Oh my God!
不可能！
There is no way!
看到尼克多痛苦了吗？
See how Nick is suffering?
这就是为什么你们不应该碰他们
This is why you guys shouldn't touch them.
我不知道你在哪里 他们是否摇摆着用趾甲碰到了你
I don't know if you're out there, if they swing and just touch you with their toenail.
就像那样？
Like that?
-你被碰了？ -对！
-But did you? -Yes!
杰克被碰了！
Jake just got touched!
嘿 我不会把你的移得太远
Hey, I won't move yours as far.
我们就把他放在这里
We'll put his right here.
我想是时候让他的线回去了 好了 现在他恢复正常了
And I think it's time to move his back. There we go, now he's back to normal.
特洛伊 我们让你觉得被针对了 所以--
Troy, we don't wanna just pick on you, so--
◎哦 我的天◎
♪ Oh my God ♪
哟！
Yo!
你无法太深入 我现在告诉你 兄弟 这要持续两天
You can't go too deep, I'm telling you now, bro, it's going on two days.
你知道你的意思是你现在必须赢
You know you're saying that you have to win now.
没人能坚持超过一天--
No one's gonna last more than a day after, like--
有趣
Interesting.
我一天之内就能赢
I'm gonna win in a day.
你必须穿过它们而不被触碰
You have to run through them without getting touched.
我们要用烟雾让他们看不见
We're gonna use the smoke to make it harder for them to see.
准备 准备 走你！
Hut, hut, hike, go!
不！
Nope!
是吗？
Was it?
-杰克 -你被碰到了！
-Jake, you got touched! -Yeah, Frankie!
准备 准备 走起！
Hut, hut, hike!
再给他点！
Give him more!
给他--
Give him--
他抓住他了！
He got him!
钱德勒 你准备好了吗？
Chandler, are you ready?
嘿 不！
Hey, no!
走起！
Hike!
哦 漏球！
Ow, fumble!
走你 2.0版本
To hike 2. 0.
哦！
Ooh!
他要自残
He hurt to himself.
所以 惩罚就是你必须在选手下面躺5分钟
So, the punishment is you have to lay under your contestant for five minutes.
我觉得我的叮咚随时都会被踢
I feel like my ding dong's gonna get kicked any second.
事实上 这还挺不错的
Oh, this kinda nice, actually.
你知道吗？ 我是个很好的激励者
You know what? I'm a great motivator.
现在你们都趴在地上了 这就完美地进入了我们的下一个环节
So now that you guys are all laying on the ground, this leads perfectly into our next segment.
克里斯 我要你拿着这个让你的人把它扔了
Chris, I need you hold this and let your guy punt it.
好吧
All right.
-哇哦！-很好！
-Whoa!- It's good!
闭嘴 我需要你的帮助 老兄
Shut up, I need your help, dude.
很好！
It's good!
-马库斯 呆在他下面 -这不公平
-Marcus, just stay under him. -It's not fair.
他为了钱德勒把薯条推得更近了 但不给我！
He pushed it up closer for Chandler, but not for me!
你应该好好尝试 你尽力了吗？
You should just get good, have you tried that?
正中！
Got him!
所以这个挑战已经持续一段时间了
So this challenge has been goin' on for a while.
-很长一段时间 -是的
-Quite some time. -Yeah.
我想是时候让财富独角兽出来了
I think it's time we bring out the Unicorn of Wealth.
把财富的独角兽丢在这里
Plop the Unicorn of Wealth right here.
我们有一些Beats 坑骗Powerbeats
We have some Beats, rip off of AirPods,
AirPods
AirPods,
我们有一台iPad、一个扬声器和一台外星笔记本电脑 供下一个退出的人使用
we have an iPad, a speaker, and an Alien ware laptop here for the next person that gets out.
这台笔记本电脑值两千美元
The laptop's worth two grand.
我知道你现在想出去 去拿吧
I know you wanna get out now, go ahead and grab it.
不 我要留下
No, I am stayin'.
可以
Okay.
-不是那些货 -不是那些？
-Not that there. -Not that?
不是那样玩意
Not that.
哦 不 马库斯！
Oh, not, Marcus!
他只是说不是那些 再多一些（就退出）
He just said not that, but he said something bigger.
你可能想和他谈谈
You might wanna have to go have a talk with him.
-你想成为连续两次第一个出局的吗？ -不会发生的
-You wanna be the first one out two times in a row? -It's not happening.
里面有很多好东西
There's a lot of good stuff in there.
哦不 一点也不感兴趣
Oh no, not interested at all.
-尼克先生 我看得出来 -他甚至都不是电脑游戏玩家
-Mr. Nick, I can tell. -Guy ain't even a PC gamer.
他不想要那些东西--
He don't want that--
尼克 去拿吧
Nick, go grab it.
那很好 但是不能接受
It's nice, but can't take it.
你刚才说什么？
What'd you just say?
我知道 阿德曼 谁先出去？
I know, Aardman, who's gonna get out first.
这就是现在的情况吗？
Is that what this is right now?
我们谈了一笔生意
I'm doing a business deal, and we're gone.
你们谈了一笔生意？
A business deal and you're gone?
我们谈了一笔生意
A business deal and we're gone.
你 什么？
You, what?
现在 这是我的问题 你要先发制人吗？
Now, here's my question. Are you gonna beat him to the punch and get off first?
我已经有决定了
I'm already on the ground.
你已经--
You're already--
所以你说你准备好了
So you're sayin' you're ready to go.
我的腿现在真的疼--
The way these legs hurting right now--
所以 尼克
So, Nick,
你公开说你在苦苦挣扎 对吧？
you openly said you're struggling, right?
我现在很挣扎
I'm struggling right now.
事情是这样的 在我出价之前 我想提醒你
So here's the thing. Before I make an offer, I wanna remind you.
你可以在未来15年里工作 赚一百万美元
One million dollars. You could work the next 15 years of your life and make a million dollars.
或者在我们举办下一个挑战的时候 你可以在强行通过并赢得最后比赛
Or you could push through and win it in a few weeks, when we have the next challenge.
言至于此 $5千美元给下一个退出的人
Having said that, $5, 000 to the first person.
哦！
Oh!
可以！
Okay!
克里斯 两个挑战你都输了
Chris, that's two challenges you lost.
我给他吃了意大利面！
I gave him linguini!
我不会成为一个更好的教练！
I couldn't have been a better coach!
你获得了$5千美元
You got offered $5, 000.
我的腿疼得厉害
My legs hurt so bad.
你现在感觉如何？
How do you feel now?
我觉得我的腿变形了
I feel like my legs are in bad shape right now.
这是个正确的决定吗？
Was it the right decision?
是的 为我的腿！
Yes, for my legs!
好吧 过来 尼克 过来
All right, come here, Nick, come on.
过来坐沙发
Come over here to the couch.
我们护送他吧
Let's escort him.
哦 嘿 钱德勒
Oh, hey Chandler.
你打盹醒来了吗？
Did you wake up from your nap?
-给你 这可以减轻你的痛苦 $5千美元 -酷
-Here you go, this should ease your pain, $5, 000. -Cool.
你没有赢$100万美元 但你有$5千
You didn't win a million dollars, but you got five grand.
他们感觉如何？
How do they feel?
-哥们 真的很伤 -是吗？
-Dude, they hurt so bad. -Do they?
你坐在上面的方式 就好像 就在这里钻孔一样
The way you sit on it, it's like, it's like digging into right here.
-我想我这里有个瘀伤 -天啊
-Think I have a bruise right here, actually. -Geez.
佩顿 你听起来已经到边缘了 所以--
Payton, you already sound like you're on the edge, so--
那不是我要找的生意 我只要把口香糖粘起来就行了
That wasn't the business deal I was looking for, I'd just stick up the gum.
所以我们已经知道 佩顿正在苦苦挣扎
So we already know, Payton's struggling.
托尼 真的是你反对奥马尔
Tony, it's really you against Omar.
你会是那个站在他面前赢得一百万美元的人吗？
Are you gonna be the one that stands up to him and wins a million dollars?
对
Yes.
因为如果奥马尔赢了 那就意味着杰克的参赛者会赢得第一个和第二个挑战
'Cause if Omar wins, that means Jake's contestant would've won the first challenge and the second.
我觉得我真的没有什么痛苦
I feel like I don't really have much pain.
如果你赢了一百万美元 你会用它买什么？
If you win the million dollars, what would you buy with it?
首先 我要回报我的家人 我的父母
Firstly, I'd give back to my whole family, my parents.
我会继续花$20万美元
$200K I'm gonna keep to spend.
-哦 只有20万？-只有20万
-Oh, only 200 grand? -Only 200.
现在我们要给所有参赛者的父母打电话
Now we're gonna call all the contestants' parents.
我们从佩顿的父亲开始
We're gonna start off with Payton's father.
对不起 你要找的人--
I'm sorry, the person you are try--
现在我们要打电话给特洛伊的妈妈
Now we're gonna call Troy's mom.
嘿 你是特洛伊的妈妈吗？
Hey, are you Troy's mother?
对
Yes.
他在秋千上荡了10个小时
He's been swinging on a swing for 10 hours,
如果他赢了 他就可以竞争一百万美元
and if he wins, he gets to compete for a million dollars.
等等 布
Just hold on, boo.
别想了 继续摇摆
Just don't think about it, just keep swinging.
哦
Aw.
随波逐流
Just go with the flow.
爸爸怎么样？
How's dad doin'?
他有好转吗？
Is he getting any better?
是的 他们点击了他的心脏去重启 然后他感觉恢复了正常
Yes, they shocked his heart to restart it, and then that makes him feel back to normal.
所以 我要去告诉他发生了什么
So, I'm gonna go and tell him what's going on.
集中精神 然后不要想 哦 我累了 还是怎么了
Just concentrate and then don't think about, like, oh, I'm tired, or something.
别想了
Just don't think about it.
不
No.
坚持住 宝贝
Just hang in there, baby.
哦 现在我要你赢
Oh, now I want you to win.
-奥马尔 出去！ -不！
-Omar, get out! -No!
可以
Okay.
我们会和下一个参赛者通电话 我们会告诉你他是怎么做到的
We're gonna hit the phone with the next contestant, we'll update you on how he does.
好的 谢谢
Okay, thank you.
好吧 好吧 晚点 妈妈
All right, all right, later, mom.
我爱你 儿子
I love you, son.
好吧 好吧
All right, all right.
好的 努力点
Okay, go hard.
-哦 -我会的
-Oh. -I will.
好吧 哇
All right, wow.
奥马尔正要给他妹妹打电话
Omar's about to call his sister.
我们只想让她加入
We're just gonna fill her in.
-嘿！ -嗨 家人！
-Hey! -Hi, homey!
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey.
所以我现在在荡秋千
So I'm currently swinging.
我做得很好 有点疼 但我基本上很好
I'm doing good, slightly sore, but I'm mostly good.
如果他今天赢了 他将在几周内挑战一百万美元
If he wins today, he competes for a million dollars in a challenge in a few weeks.
所以 如果他处理得当 他可能成为百万富翁
So, if he plays his cards right, he could become a millionaire.
所以我希望你能鼓励他 给他一些动力
So I want you to just encourage him and give him some motivation.
我把手机还他
I'm gonna hand him back.
继续摇摆 继续前进 只是 呃 不管它有多长
Keep swinging, keep going, it's just, uh, however long it is.
别担心
Don't worry about it.
稍后再谈
Talk to you soon.
-结束给我打电话 -是的 我会的
-Call me after. -Yes, I will.
除了佩顿每个人都有一点动力
Everyone just got a little bit of motivation except for Payton.
你知道吗？
You know what?
-我们在荡秋千！-是啊！
-We're swingin'! -Yeah!
所以保持摇摆！
So just keep swingin'!
是 啊！
Yeah!
喔！
Whoo!
克里斯 我哥哥 你能把史蒂夫送上赛场吗？
Chris, my brother, can you cart Steve onto the court?
哦哦
Uh-oh.
如果你现在出去 你可以得到所有的礼物
If you get out now, you can have all the presents.
马库斯！
Marcus!
-马库斯睡着了 -熟睡
-Marcus is asleep. -Sound asleep.
嘿 伙计
Hey buddy.
你知道我们怎么录的吗？
You know how we're recording these?
看你们怎么评价？
See how do y'all rate?
你已经尽力了
You did the best you could do.
谢谢你能来 你知道我在说什么吗？
Appreciate you comin' out here, you know what I'm sayin'?
我和马库斯在今天的挑战赛中有点起起落落
Me and Marcus had a little bit of up and downs during our challenge today.
是的 我们做到了 我们做到了 我们做到了
Yeah, we did, we did, we did.
但我想我们是在马库斯睡着的时候克服的
But I think we overcame'em when Marcus fell asleep.
我认为你是对的
I think you're right.
他们已经荡了12个小时了
They've been swinging for 12 hours.
12小时 12小时！
12 hours, 12 hours!
哦 太好了
Ooh, that was nice.
我觉得你们两个都要去一段时间
I have a feeling you're both gonna go a while.
你会这么说吗？
Would you say so?
我想我们会慢慢来的！
I guess we'll just do a time lapse!
上一个最后下落挑战最终是杰克和钱德勒的的选手
So the last to fall challenge came down to Jake's contestant and Chandler's.
所以这是完全相同的事情
So this is the exact same thing.
除此之外 杰克晚上还在这里 钱德勒没有
On top of that, Jake was still here at night time, Chandler wasn't.
不过 改变历史 特洛伊
Change history, though, Troy.
我相信
I believe.
我会改的
I will change it.
我不知道你们这么做
I don't know you guys do this.
我累了
I'm tired.
现在是早上六点
It is six AM.
我知道你们一定很累
I know you guys have to be tired.
我感觉很好 吉米
I'm feeling great, Jimmy.
我不明白他是怎么想的
I don't get how he feels like that.
-我感觉很好 -早上六点
-I feel great. -At six AM in the morning.
我感觉很好 老兄 我感觉很好
I feel great, dude, I feel great.
-你本来可以去一天的 -是啊！
-You could've gone a day. -Yeah!
特洛伊 你还要继续吗？
Troy, you still gonna go on?
稍微离开一点 守着桌子 但你就在那里 还是你只是在拖？
A little off, guard the table, but that's where you are, or are you just dragging?
我快疯了
I'm going off beat.
让我咨询一下团队
Lemme consult the team.
我想和队员商量 但队员们都睡着了
I wanted to consult with the team, but the team's asleep.
我可能提供一些钱 你知道 看看谁要去拿
I might offer some money, you know, to see who takes it.
好吧 我们试试钱德勒
Okay, let's try Chandler.
我们给他们钱 看有没有人想退出
We're offering them money to see if anyone wants to get out.
你想来劝你的人留下来吗？
Do you wanna come talk your guy into staying?
他好像睡着了
He's like, asleep.
可以
Okay.
所以我们叫醒了杰克 我们叫醒了钱德勒
So we woke up Jake, and we woke up Chandler.
现在我们去引诱他们一些钱
Now let's go offer them some money.
恭喜你 你醒了
Congratulations, you're awake.
你知道我们是怎么做事的
You know how we do things.
有时候人们只需要一点点的推动就可以离开 你同意吗 钱德勒？
Sometimes people just need a little bit of a nudge to get out, would you agree, Chandler?
对
Yes.
在接下来的30秒里 如果有人出去 $1万美元
For the next 30 seconds, if someone gets out, $10, 000.
-一万 -那可是一大笔钱
-10, 000. -That's a lot of money.
奥马尔 我知道你想要$1万美元
Omar, I know you want this $10, 000.
-不 我没有 -你能用它买什么？
-Nah, I don't. -What could you buy with it?
-我不想要 -不 我没有
-I don't want it. -No, I don't.
我要拿一百万 我从一开始就决定了
I'm going for the million, and I decided that from the start.
你在想什么 特洛伊？
What's going through your mind, Troy?
我想要一百万 伙计
I wanna get that one mil, man.
你想得到一百万吗？
You wanna get the million?
但即使你在这里赢了 你还是要在这之后再赢一场挑战
But even if you win here, you still have to win another challenge after this.
你不可能在同一个场景中赢得比赛 但你可以少受点苦
You could not win that and be in the same scenario, but with way less suffering.
是啊 奥马尔 你脸上一直挂着微笑
Yeah, Omar, you've had a smile on your face this whole time.
是啊 当你赢的时候为什么不笑着去做呢？
Yeah, why not do it with a smile when you're winning?
你现在会接受这笔交易吗？
Would you have taken that deal now?
来吧奥马尔 让我赢吧 伙计
C'mon Omar, just let me win, man.
布鲁 我明天才离开 你想留下就留下
Bruh, I'm not leaving 'til tomorrow, you can stay if you want to.
相信我 我这么说 你是在浪费时间 我不会走的
Trust me when I say this, you're wasting your time, I'm not leaving.
你的能量 我想要 我需要！
The energy you have, I want that, I need that!
你准备好了吗？
Are you givin' up?
老兄 我现在要崩溃了
Dude, I'm breaking right now.
别 老兄 别摔坏了
Do not, dude, don't break.
我身体上很痛
I am physically, like, hurting so bad.
特洛伊
Troy.
你感觉怎么样？
How are you feeling?
我受伤了
I'm hurting.
可以
Okay.
我看得出你很伤心
I can tell you're hurting.
所以如果有人在接下来的30秒内离开 我将给他们$1万美元的现金
So if someone gets out in the next 30 seconds, I will give them $10, 000 in cash.
如果我赢了一百万 我就给他百分之一的奖金
I'm gonna give him one percent of my winnings if I win the million.
哦 我没听到！-我告诉他了
Oh, I didn't hear that!- I told him that.
如果奥马尔赢了 他将面对阿基拉和接下来两个挑战的赢家
If Omar wins, he's gonna face up against Akira and the winners of the next two challenges
-赢了这件事 -为了一百万美元
-And win off this thing. -For a million dollars.
你可以得到1万美元 你可能还会得到1万美元
You get 10 grand, and you can potentially get another 10 grand.
哥们 我至少还能再呆一天
Dude, I could go for at least one more day.
特洛伊 好吧 再给他30秒
Troy, all right, give him another 30 seconds.
一百万 你听到了 我需要它
A million, you heard it, I need it.
这就是决心
This is determination right there.
继续战斗 继续战斗
Keep fightin', keep fightin'.
奥马尔——我活下来了
Omar is--- I'm surviving.
好吧 特洛伊
All right, Troy.
坚持下去
Stick it out and go,
或者你今天可以带着2万块钱离开
or you could walk away today with 20 grand.
我知道那会对你的家庭有很大帮助
I know that would help your family greatly.
所以奥马尔现在在$1万美元的基础上再加上2%
So Omar has now offered two percent on top of the $10, 000.
由于你们有些人的数学不是很好 如果他赢了一百万美元
And since some of you aren't that good with math, if he wins a million dollars,
百分之二看起来不算多 但仍然是2万美元
two percent might not seem like a lot, but that's still 20 grand.
我感觉不太好
I'm not feeling so good.
如果他起来了 好吧 如果你想不想继续的话 完全取决于你
If he gets up, okay, 100% up to you if you wanna keep going or not.
奥马尔是赢家！
Omar is the winner!
我们打个平局吧！
Let's have a draw!
你没有--
You didn't--
我都不知道该说什么 伙计
I don't even know what to say, man.
你杀了它
You killed it.
你得到了一万块的保证
You got guaranteed 10 grand.
如果奥马尔赢了 你还有20分
If Omar wins, you get another 20.
我知道这肯定会有帮助
And I know that'll help for sure.
所以 我为你感到骄傲
So, I'm proud of you.
每个人都为你骄傲
Everyone's proud of you.
你妈妈 你的家人肯定会为你骄傲的
Your mom, your family's gonna be proud of you for sure.
是的 我在这里感觉好多了
Yeah, I feel better up here.
我真的很想赢球 打破那种连败的感觉
I really wanted to win it to break, you know, the losing streak.
这就是为什么？
That's why?
好吧 我很感激你帮我 伙计 但那太棒了
Well, I appreciate you trying for me, man, but that was awesome.
你现在就可以拿到$1万美元了
And you're gonna get that $10, 000 now.
我要感谢我的粉丝和我的家人
Gotta give thanks to my fans, and my family.
我肯定会给你$2万美元的 兄弟
I'mma give you that $20K, for sure, bro,
100% 你会得到$2万美元
100%, you'll gain that $20K.
-杰克 阿基拉赢了 -是的
-Jake, Akira won. -Yes.
奥马尔赢了 你两个赢了
Omar won, you're two for two.
两个哦
Two and oh.
这意味着四个人中的两个将是你的人
Which means two of the four people competing for a million dollars will be your guys.
说实话 一百万对我来说意义重大
Honestly, one million means a lot to me.
就像 我的家人一辈子都在照顾我
And like, my family has taken care of me all my life.
我只想回报他们 这似乎是个完美的机会
And all I want to do is like give back to them, and this seems like the perfect opportunity
通过 像 得到一百万
through, like, getting a million.
根据上一段视频中的评论部分 人们真的很喜欢Akira
Based on the comments section up in the last video, people really like Akira.
好吧 我们看看他们对你的反应 奥马尔
Well, we'll see how they respond to you, Omar.
几周后见
And we'll see you in a few weeks.